sup everyone chambers wanted to do a
five here at the very special video so
as you can tell by the gate of today
today is Christmas so of course I
figured you know why not
how about I show are a lot more
so I figured so I figured okay to
let me move this some I made him
a
he's saying is I figured you know what
it's Christmas I might as well show my
fans fly nothing in what I got got for
Christmas so no I do not get a sock sock
Hedrick foxy I wish I did sock is just
here because well I guess as he wants to
be here just so sock you be good all you
be good don't touch my presence the
Mandy will you be good alright so first
up I got this that's right everyone
another sock on dr. marks revenge TVs as
you know this is my all-time favorite
Sonic Underground DVD probably got like
six of them but to be honest I was kind
of disappointed when my parents put this
in my hand I mean I opened it and this
was always inside nothing up in
this
I mean I'm not a lot of screamed I got
so angry
I thought they lost the deviant store I
was about to force them chug that down
until oh no they said they said they
forgot to put money in it when they had
to be because they were going to trick
me by give me a talk on DVD and with
actual money being inside of it can you
believe that stuff Howard that would
make me happy no I mean I'm not allowed
to attach him I was I was tired of the
arrived there
I mean I I just wanted you to go to bed
I mean back with Miss Emma anyway
things kind of cool down a bit after
they remind me
you know what just just go go take the
money by own their DVDs I mean that
beginner like like like like 15 bucks or
something so yeah so yeah 50 bucks
the DVDs cost about 39 I can get so I
guess I can get like four of them song
next enough you know really pissed me
off is they gave me this they gave
me this for for Christmas that's
right the green Teletubby Dipsy or some
I don't know I guess from this
thing they mouth I was Manic guy I don't
know the when when they had a game I had
to tell me my favorite character ever
even thought then I had to tell them no
I do not like Manic Bobby's my favorite
character ever
and besides it's either your Manic it's
a teletovic I mean I mean
get over oh yeah that's my pumpkin pie
I'm eating it right now
anyway they weren't done with action cuz
of me afterwards day gave me this I big
thought it was Knuckles like
no huh cop that Nick how would
Lexi I'm like allows I'm pretty happy
with this I got this I got this thing
now as you all know I'm a big fan of the
M&M guy so you know the red and yellow
the red and yellow
mmm guys go pinochle no solution because
just because that mmm kids remember yeah
so anyway well there's something in
there how to get it open and many open
there there there we go
well inside was that thing like it's no
I yeah I like them and I'm characters 3
for mommy else not gonna get like this
one on your Knuckles I'm doing like a
Sonic green one more than radical that
next of course I since I love the
mmm you know I guess I could use all my
money actively put this over here
anyways next litter that stuff I wanna
next uh then that's what I got me really
happy like as you may know I love Star
Wars I lost our card love them mmm girl
got those two got this one the
best puppy a lot of - boom believe this
no this one my personal favorite the
yellow one looks like Bobby oh yes this
one not as cool but Lots up this is
raw look at that
I couldn't believe that I mean I could
is imagine inside Bobby
lighting like sticking up on Sarge boho
who knows what a fine okay next my mom
my mom and daddy they got me I want to
see the new style movie it was bitchin
so be and of course I love Star Wars so
so they bought me all the the main cast
oh the new selling really got me collar
room right then they got that yeah you
can extend
oh yeah there we go Oh like a collar man
duh I got that oh my God he's tall
what the that is
anyways I got a generic still what I saw
was a generic youtuber - I was it was
pod amory and the white dude
so yeah the wat dude they die
they just get made him an evade you were
too lazy do my head so they just gave
him a stormtrooper thing and the
black guy now God I love it like
that I'm excuse my yeah all that
and I love I guard me like he fits
so well with the rest of my fingers
namely mommy my mace windu figure if you
know what I mean
go black people beat the wipe your asses
no that's how it's done
so yeah yeah I I guess that's my
Christmas haul Merry Christmas I
how about you tell me what you guys got
in the comments I'll be I'll be glad to
hear ah
boom